Karen A. Largent

130 Betcher Road, Collegeville, PA 19426 610-209-6865 | <u>kalargent@gmail.com</u>

Github: https://github.com/kalargent

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/karen-largent-ab01494/

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Seasoned software professional and rising Full Stack Engineer who brings deep experience in identifying and defining product features and enhancements. Proven professional record building and leading agile teams, and delivering quality product functionality that strengthens products in the market.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Languages/Libraries: JavaScript, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Sequelize, Mongoose, Handlebars
- Frameworks: Bootstrap, Materialize
- Databases: SQL, MongoDB
- Deployment: Heroku, GitHub Pages
- Version Control: Git
- Software: MacOS, Visual Studio Code, Atlassian Jira and Confluence, Microsoft Team Foundation Server, ProductBoard

RECENT PROJECTS

Memory Game

Octocat themed memory game. To win, don't click the same image more than once.

GitHub: https://github.com/kalargent/clicking-with-marnie | Deployed: (TBD)

- Sole Developer
- First project created with ReactJS

Eat Da Burger

Allows users to move burgers to and from different lists to indicate when one is eaten or on the menu.

GitHub: https://github.com/kalargent/eat-da-burger | Video: https://embed.vidyard.com/watch/8pqDkyB8KGUa2t9GcKHog9

- Sole Developer
- NodeJS, MySQL, ExpressJS, Handlebars, Hand-coded Object Relational Mapper (ORM)

Site Scraper

Scrapes a website for articles, allows users to save articles to favorites, view favorites, and add notes.

GitHub: https://github.com/kalargent/site-scrape | Deployed: https://warm-journey-95389.herokuapp.com

- Sole Developer
- NodeJS, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery, AJAX, MongoDB, ExpressJS, Mongoose, Handlebars

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Relay Network | Radnor, PA

Product Manager

December 2017 - May 2019

- Identified and specify product features and requirements with Epics and User Stories
- Improved development throughput by guiding a small agile team of engineers through a transition from Scrum to Kanban
- Focused on minimum viable product to shorten delivery cycles and improve feedback loops on new features and enhancements
- Acted as scrum master, running regular ceremonies and removing roadblocks.

Ring Solutions, formerly Zonoff, Inc. | Malvern, PA

Senior Product Manager

March 2017 - December 2017

- Defined and documented the user stories for the user flow to arm and disarm a DIY home security project
- Defined and documented the user stories for the user flow to setup a DIY home security project
- Defined features for an internal support portal that enabled CS agents to resolve customer issues quickly and efficiently and worked with an Agile development team to complete the portal in time for the products to hit the shelf, against aggressive deadlines
- Mapped current CS processed in an effort to identify opportunities for improvement
- Collaborated with CS leadership to open and staff a 100-seat call center in three months, including purchasing, space design
- Designed and implemented a training program and successfully trained 100+ new hires in 5 months

Zonoff, Inc. | Malvern, PA

Senior Product Manager

March 2017 - December 2017

- Completed competitive analysis and proposed roadmap items based on research. Developed initial business cases that opened the product into new markets.
- Worked with the business, architects, development, and QA to author epics and user stories. Continuously define and iterate on those artifacts during grooming and within sprints.
- Acted as primary contact to multiple clients to gather requirements for customizing and branding Zonoff's Z1 platform to meet their needs
- Supported and mentored 5 development teams simultaneously during sprints to clarify acceptance criteria and close gaps, and identify and triage blockers

PREVIOUS EMPLOYMENT

Senior Business Analyst, YPrime, 2014=2015 | QVC, Senior Business Analyst, 2013-2014 Almac Group, Senior Business Analyst, 2012, 2013 | Citi Prepaid Services, Assistant Vice President, 2011-2012

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Product Management | Epic and User Story Definition | Team Building | Business Analysis | Technical Writing | Leading and Influencing Teams

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate, Pennsylvania University, 2019 (anticipated)
Certified Scrum Product Owner (CSPO), Scrum Alliance, 2003 - Present
B.A., English Literature, The Pennsylvania State University • 2001

References Available Upon Request